<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ELVIS 75 on 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible</title>
    <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ELVIS 75 on 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Phillip Remaker, except where noted, 1975 -</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://eldo.remaker.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible Survival Guide</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/survivalguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 19:20:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/survivalguide/</guid>
      <description>Since first setting up my Cadillac page, I have been surprised and flattered to get questions from fellow Cadillac Owners. I am relatively new to owning a classic Cadillac, but I am happy to help. This page is an assembly of lessons, resources, and stories that I have collected along the way from generous fellow enthusiasts. The most helpful bunch of enthusiasts on the net had been the good folks on The Cadillac Mailing List which was part of Yahoo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stork Rules for Buying a Classic Cadillac</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/storkrules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 19:20:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/storkrules/</guid>
      <description>A compilation of this wisdom was mailed to the list at my request (&amp;ldquo;What ARE these Stork Rules that everyone keeps talking about?&amp;quot;), and I reproduce that list here. It is slightly edited for clarity.
  It must be a one owner car. If possible the one owner should be elderly and female, and the car should have been stalked in the parking lot of the local church, bingo or senior center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walnut Creek for Surgery</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/surgery/</guid>
      <description>The question today boys and girls is:
What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between interior parts of a 1975 Eldorado Coupe and a Convertible?
Thankfully, the answer is &amp;ldquo;not a lot!&amp;rdquo;
Thanks to Stephan&amp;rsquo;s incredible generosity, the non-original interior from his recently acquired parts hardtop coupe (&amp;quot;The Big Blue Beater&amp;quot;) has been transplanted into my 1975 Convertible. So,I have gone fron an Antique Light Blue interior to a dark blue non-original interior. It is quite can improvement over my dramatically rotting seats which I refused to spend over $1500 to re-cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If it&#39;s worth doing, it&#39;s worth overdoing</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/noeldorado/xmas2005/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/noeldorado/xmas2005/</guid>
      <description>For 2005, I got the crazy idea to add MORE lights to the Cadillac. With around 300 mini lights, My tired old WalMart Inverter struggled mightily under the load. When the car idled, the lights went din, or whout off altogether. The whole set would randomly shut down.
At work, I complained to my friend Rick who nodded patiently and empathtically at my predicament.
The next morning, he dropped off a giant 300W inverter with long tail of 10 gauge silvered wire terminated with endpoints designed for direct car battery connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Roe&#39;s Guide to the Long Term Maintenace of Old GM Cars</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/bruce-roe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/bruce-roe/</guid>
      <description>Bruce Roe&amp;rsquo;s (bcroe@juno.com) Guide to the Long Term Maintenace of Old GM Cars
Edited by Phil Remaker (spamtrap-pr1@remaker.com)
[Editor: Have you ever noticed how most service manuals stop dead at 100,000 miles? That is because no manufacturer wants you to keep a car that long. Bruce Roe, a regular contributor to The Cadillac Mailing List frequently shares his wisdom about maintaining his older GM cars which are WELL past the 100,000 mile mark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Noëldorado Christmas 2004</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/noeldorado/noeldorado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/noeldorado/noeldorado/</guid>
      <description>This Christmas for the first time in a few years, I was not traveling. My kids, 6 and 8, are into the holiday decorating. We did the tree and the house, but something was missing.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to decorate the 1975 Eldorado Convertible with Christmas lights ever since I got it. I even pictured in my mind what it looked like. It just BEGS to be driven, with the top down, surrounded in lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Cruz and San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/santacruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/santacruz/</guid>
      <description>I had planned to cruise to LA this week in my 1975 Eldorado Convertible, but my &amp;ldquo;shotgun&amp;rdquo; cancelled at the last minute due to a family illness. I was bummed, but didn&amp;rsquo;t feel up to making the 350+ mile trek to LA by myself. So I was feeling a little sorry for myself when I found this out on Thursday, so I set off to make the most of my weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid Life Madness</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/midlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/midlife/</guid>
      <description>Shhh, Its a secret. An idea. Madness. Total madness, even.
On the weekend of 6/25/2004, I have a vision: An idea that is insane, indefensible, and whatever other in-word you can think of.
My wife and kids&amp;hellip; gone. Sean&amp;rsquo;s wife and kids&amp;hellip; gone. Steve&amp;rsquo;s wife and kids&amp;hellip; understanding of Steve&amp;rsquo;s need for a break.
My car has a new suspension. It looks like crap, but it can drive.
It can drive a long way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Live and Drive in LA</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/toliveanddriveinla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/adventures/toliveanddriveinla/</guid>
      <description>The philosophy of this cruise is to pack as much tourist-crap-you-can-do-in-a-covertible into a weekend trip, 12 hours of which is already eaten up getting to and from the greater LA Metroplitian area. The basic idea is to drive everywhere that you have heard of, eat at only famous places, and find every boulevard even mentioned in a rock and roll song and drive down it.
Driving
 Mulholland between Cahuenga and Coldwater Canyon Ledgewood drive to the Hollywood Sign Hollywood between La Brea and Argyle Colorado Boulevard in Pasadena The 110 to the 105 to Crenshaw Boulevard Santa Monica Boulevard  Dining</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining and repairing the notorious and legendary GM scissortop</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/scissortop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/scissortop/</guid>
      <description>Copyright ©2003 by Derek J. Sherwood
Reproduced with permission courtesy of Derek J. Sherwood (dsherwoo at ycp dot edu)
Version: 26 May 2003
It finally happened &amp;ndash; the unthinkable. You&amp;rsquo;ve just dusted off your pride and joy after a long, hard winter, and are sitting in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat in your garage, about to put the top down for the first time in several months, anticipating good weather ahead. You press the switch and&amp;hellip;nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Summary of Auto Refrigerants</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/refrigerants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/maintenance/refrigerants/</guid>
      <description>Hat tip to Craig M Séman, owner of the (now defunct) Cadillac Craft Center in Midland, NC
Reprinted from The Cadillac Mailing List from the (now defunct) Yahoo Groups.
When I do A/C work whether it be R12 or R134a I run a VOV (Variable Orifice Valve) regardless.
All of this discussion of refrigerant replacements is all well and good but here is the catch, most of us are doing work on our own cars or people&amp;rsquo;s cars where the envrionment is tightly controlled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buying the Beast</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/why/thebeginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/why/thebeginning/</guid>
      <description>1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible &amp;ldquo;ELVIS75&amp;rdquo;
1975 Cadillac Eldorado convertible, 500 cubic inch (That&amp;rsquo;s 8.2 liter, for you metric folks) 190HP engine, &amp;ldquo;Gossamer Blue Metallic Firemist&amp;rdquo; exterior with white top and &amp;ldquo;Light Antique Blue&amp;rdquo; interior. Power everything: top, windows, steering, 6-way power 50/50 seats with armrest, complete with Delco factory AM/FM 8-track deck, Class III towing package. Obligatory fuzzy dice on rearview mirror. Outside temperature gauge on drivers side mirror. Vanity plates read &amp;ldquo;ELVIS 75&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer of 1977</title>
      <link>http://eldo.remaker.com/why/summer1977/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 1977 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eldo.remaker.com/why/summer1977/</guid>
      <description>My First 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Experience
Summer 1977, at the New Jersey shore. Disco. Pinball. Pong. And the 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible.
My dad borrowed a cherry 1975 convertible from his doctor friend who was out of town for the summer. We had a blast in it. It had power everything: windows, locks, climate control, antenna and roof. It had an 8 track stereo and a 40-channel CB radio. This is back when CB was cool, mind you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
