<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maintenance on 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible</title>
    <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maintenance on 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Phillip Remaker, except where noted, 1975 -</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 19:20:55 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible Survival Guide</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/survivalguide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 19:20:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/survivalguide/</guid>
      <description>Since first setting up my Cadillac page, I have been surprised and flattered to get questions from fellow Cadillac Owners. I am relatively new to owning a classic Cadillac, but I am happy to help. This page is an assembly of lessons, resources, and stories that I have collected along the way from generous fellow enthusiasts. The most helpful bunch of enthusiasts on the net had been the good folks on The Cadillac Mailing List which was part of Yahoo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stork Rules for Buying a Classic Cadillac</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/storkrules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 19:20:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/storkrules/</guid>
      <description>A compilation of this wisdom was mailed to the list at my request (&amp;ldquo;What ARE these Stork Rules that everyone keeps talking about?&amp;quot;), and I reproduce that list here. It is slightly edited for clarity.
  It must be a one owner car. If possible the one owner should be elderly and female, and the car should have been stalked in the parking lot of the local church, bingo or senior center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Roe&#39;s Guide to the Long Term Maintenace of Old GM Cars</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/bruce-roe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/bruce-roe/</guid>
      <description>Bruce Roe&amp;rsquo;s (bcroe@juno.com) Guide to the Long Term Maintenace of Old GM Cars
Edited by Phil Remaker (spamtrap-pr1@remaker.com)
[Editor: Have you ever noticed how most service manuals stop dead at 100,000 miles? That is because no manufacturer wants you to keep a car that long. Bruce Roe, a regular contributor to The Cadillac Mailing List frequently shares his wisdom about maintaining his older GM cars which are WELL past the 100,000 mile mark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintaining and repairing the notorious and legendary GM scissortop</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/scissortop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/scissortop/</guid>
      <description>Copyright ©2003 by Derek J. Sherwood
Reproduced with permission courtesy of Derek J. Sherwood (dsherwoo at ycp dot edu)
Version: 26 May 2003
It finally happened &amp;ndash; the unthinkable. You&amp;rsquo;ve just dusted off your pride and joy after a long, hard winter, and are sitting in the driver&amp;rsquo;s seat in your garage, about to put the top down for the first time in several months, anticipating good weather ahead. You press the switch and&amp;hellip;nothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Summary of Auto Refrigerants</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/refrigerants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2003 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/maintenance/refrigerants/</guid>
      <description>Hat tip to Craig M Séman, owner of the (now defunct) Cadillac Craft Center in Midland, NC
Reprinted from The Cadillac Mailing List from the (now defunct) Yahoo Groups.
When I do A/C work whether it be R12 or R134a I run a VOV (Variable Orifice Valve) regardless.
All of this discussion of refrigerant replacements is all well and good but here is the catch, most of us are doing work on our own cars or people&amp;rsquo;s cars where the envrionment is tightly controlled.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
