<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adventures on 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible</title>
    <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Adventures on 1975 Cadillac Eldorado Convertible</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Phillip Remaker, except where noted, 1975 -</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 19:20:55 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Walnut Creek for Surgery</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/surgery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/surgery/</guid>
      <description>The question today boys and girls is:
What&amp;rsquo;s the difference between interior parts of a 1975 Eldorado Coupe and a Convertible?
Thankfully, the answer is &amp;ldquo;not a lot!&amp;rdquo;
Thanks to Stephan&amp;rsquo;s incredible generosity, the non-original interior from his recently acquired parts hardtop coupe (&amp;quot;The Big Blue Beater&amp;quot;) has been transplanted into my 1975 Convertible. So,I have gone fron an Antique Light Blue interior to a dark blue non-original interior. It is quite can improvement over my dramatically rotting seats which I refused to spend over $1500 to re-cover.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Santa Cruz and San Francisco</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/santacruz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/santacruz/</guid>
      <description>I had planned to cruise to LA this week in my 1975 Eldorado Convertible, but my &amp;ldquo;shotgun&amp;rdquo; cancelled at the last minute due to a family illness. I was bummed, but didn&amp;rsquo;t feel up to making the 350+ mile trek to LA by myself. So I was feeling a little sorry for myself when I found this out on Thursday, so I set off to make the most of my weekend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mid Life Madness</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/midlife/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/midlife/</guid>
      <description>Shhh, Its a secret. An idea. Madness. Total madness, even.
On the weekend of 6/25/2004, I have a vision: An idea that is insane, indefensible, and whatever other in-word you can think of.
My wife and kids&amp;hellip; gone. Sean&amp;rsquo;s wife and kids&amp;hellip; gone. Steve&amp;rsquo;s wife and kids&amp;hellip; understanding of Steve&amp;rsquo;s need for a break.
My car has a new suspension. It looks like crap, but it can drive.
It can drive a long way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To Live and Drive in LA</title>
      <link>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/toliveanddriveinla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://1975eldoradoconvertible.com/adventures/toliveanddriveinla/</guid>
      <description>The philosophy of this cruise is to pack as much tourist-crap-you-can-do-in-a-covertible into a weekend trip, 12 hours of which is already eaten up getting to and from the greater LA Metroplitian area. The basic idea is to drive everywhere that you have heard of, eat at only famous places, and find every boulevard even mentioned in a rock and roll song and drive down it.
Driving
 Mulholland between Cahuenga and Coldwater Canyon Ledgewood drive to the Hollywood Sign Hollywood between La Brea and Argyle Colorado Boulevard in Pasadena The 110 to the 105 to Crenshaw Boulevard Santa Monica Boulevard  Dining</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
